《越狱》剧情回顾
Previously on Prison Break.
国土安全局有人
Someone at Homeland Security did an enhanced
通过图片查了你的信息
image search on you today.
是谁
Who?
他叫当·赛尔夫
His name is Don Self.
说
Yes.
你最好把你手上
What do you say you give me that little
那张纸给我
piece of paper in your hand.
从现在开始
From now on, I'm asking
我要求每一个人在任何时候
that everyone keep their card on them
都要把卡带在身上
at all times.
那本书呢
Where's the bird book?
书
Bird book?
书在什么地方
Where's the book?!
有人跟踪我
Someone was following me.
-是不是这个人  -是的
-Is this the guy? -Yeah.
这个人是谁
Who's that?
杀我儿子的人
That's the man who killed my son.
现在他冲我们来了
Now he's come to kill us.
可别上瘾啊
Don't get used to it.
神奇小子 8号门
SparkleKid, Gate 8.
对不起
Excuse me.
你好
Hi, there.
我想下几个注
I would like to place some bets, please.
我想把注下到第一场的
Uh, I'd like to place an exacta
布罗迪队长和琥珀先生
on Captain Brody and Mister Hooper in the first race.
没问题
All right.
20块 谢谢
$20, please.
谢谢
Thank you.
我想你下错注了
I think you made a mistake here.
我想下的是
I wanted a quinella
布罗迪队长和琥珀先生赢得前两名
for Captain Brody and Mister Hooper in the first race.
可你却错投成了正序连赢
Uh, you gave me an exacta.
我是按照你的要求下注的
That's what you told me you wanted.
我不是这么告诉你的
No, it's not what I told you.
我要你给我改回来
And I want you to fix it!
先生  我是按你要求下注的
Sir, I gave you exactly what you asked...
不  你不是  这到底是什么鬼地方
No, you didn't-- What the hell kind of place is this?!
-请你冷静一下  -我没有
-If you'll just calm down, please. -I'm not--
让我冷静  你什么意思
Calm down? What-what are you talking about?
给我改回来
I want you to fix this.
这是  你给我的
This is-- you gave me
是下错注的  我压的是
the wrong bet. I placed a bet
布罗迪队长和琥珀先生
on a quinella on Doctor Brody
在第一场比赛赢得前两名
and Mister Hooper in the first race.
有人在投注口
Yo, somebody's freaking out
-对投注员大喊大叫  -我这就去看看
-on one of the clerks inside. -We'll check it out.
路易斯  投注口出了一些问题
Hey, Louis, we've got a disturbance by the windows.
我这就来
I'm on my way.
这到底是什么鬼地方
What the hell kind of place is this anyway?!
-请你冷静一下  -我没有
-If you'll just calm down, please. -I'm not...
你到底什么意思
What, what are you talking about?
我要你给我改回来
I want you to fix this!
这是  你给我下错注了
This is-- You gave me the wrong bet.
是第一场比赛  不是猜第一第二
For the first race not an exacta.
你给我的是猜第一第二的
You gave me an exacta.
-你就是那么告诉我的  -我没那么做
-That's what you told me. -I didn't give you...
你挡住后面的人了
You're holding up the line.
如果你不介意的话
Please, if you don't mind...
不和管事的谈谈  我就不走
I'm not leaving this place until I talk to the guy...
先生  不要激动
Sir, if you could just not get hysterical.
-我没激动  -先生  先生
-I'm not getting hysterical! -Sir, sir, sir, sir.
-你需要冷静一下  -你又是谁
-Hey, you need to calm down. -Who the hell are you?
我是经理  不要激动
I'm the operations manager, all right. Take it easy.
你不查你工作人员的背景吗
Do you run background checks on your employees
还是你聘用坐过牢的人
or do you just let cons work here?
没有那种人在这里工作
Okay, there are no cons working here, all right?
你看她  她不是吗
Look at her. What is she doing?
梅芙  你有案底吗  梅芙
Ma-Mave-Mave, do you have a record, Mave?
对不起  先生
Excuse me. Sir, hey!
够了  冷静一下  先生
That's enough. Calm down, sir.
-你在敷衍我  -我没有
-You're patronizing me. -I'm not.
我现在遇着麻烦了  你到底是来帮我解决问题的
I got a problem here. Did you come to help me
还是来给我添麻烦的
or did you come to give me a hard time?
-我是来帮你的  -你是来帮我的 那好
-I came to help you. -You came to help me, okay.
不好意思  小姐
Excuse me, Miss.
哦
Oh.
太感谢你了
Oh, my God. Thank you so much.
如果我把这些东西丢了
I would have been in so much trouble
我就麻烦大了  你可不知道我老板
if I'd lost those. You don't know my boss.
他甚至会
He would have gone up
把我生吞活剥
one side of me and down the other.
-太谢谢你了  -不客气
-Thank you. -Any time.
你看她  看她看我的眼神  你为什么
Look at her-- Why is she lookin' at me like that? Why are you looking
-那么看着我  -别冲着别人喊 可以吗？
-looking at me like that? -Let's not yell at anyone, all right?
我们会处理这个问题的  我需要先...
We'll take care of it. I just need to get...
我没喊
I'm not yelling at anyone.
对不起啊
Oh, sorry, sir.
我盯着监视器
I'll keep an eye on the monitors.
他要回来了
He's heading back.
我们走
Let's go.
-情况怎么样  -信号很强
-How's it look? -I'm getting a clear signal.
都准备好了
We're all set.
4号持卡人  轮到你了
Cardholder number four, you're up.
给你  亲爱的
Here you go, darling.
谢谢
Yeah. Thanks.
计时员说神奇小子今天
The clocker said SparkleKid was edging
在准备的时候就接近记录了
on the track record at prep.
太好了  亲爱的
Oh, that's great, honey.
我们走
Let's go.
大家下午好
Good afternoon, ladies and gentlemen
欢迎来到今天的第一场比赛
welcome to the first race of the day here at Los Alamitos.
比赛马匹都在门前了  一切准备就绪
The starters are at the gate... and we're ready to go.
它们开始跑了
And they're off and running.
真见鬼
What the hell?
哦  有马困住了  门卡了  门卡了
Oh, we have a stall! It's stuck, it's stuck. The gate's stuck.
我要去找经理谈谈
I'll go talk to the manager.
本字幕由YYeTs人人影视翻译制作
更多字幕下载 请登陆 www.YYeTs.net
■
字幕：YYeTs人人影视字幕组  后期：zwzy_1007(胖胖)
《越狱》第四季 第六集
Prison.Break.S04E06
我要见经理
I need to see the manager.
好的  先生
Yes, sir.
对刚才发生的事情
You better have a damn good explanation
你最好给我一个好的解释
about what just happened.
我一会再打给你
All right, I'll get back to you.
我们正在查  埃迪森先生
We're looking into it right now, Mr. Edison.
现在放录像
Cue up the tape. Now.
已经接收信号了
We've made contact.
15%  还在继续
15% and counting.
就那  门卡住了
Right there, it's stuck.
那扇门出什么问题了
What happened to his gate?!
我不知道
I-I don't know.
路易斯  你最好现在过来一下
Lewis you better come down here.
现在不行
Not now.
我们在8号门发现了一些东西
We found something on Gate 8 where SparkleKid was placed.
我马上就回来
I'll be right back.
我和你一起去
I'm coming with you.
都收到了吗
Did we get it?
100%  全有  卡的内容全有
100% We're all there.Card's all there.
你不要和输的人开玩笑
You've never jerked a loser before.
都是你的错
It's all your fault!
需要支援
We're gonna need some backup.
警察来了  你最好在被发现之前离开这里
Here come the cops. You better go before you get recognized.
-必须有人放风  -我来放风  快走
-Someone has to be lookout. -I'll take care of it.Go! Go!
行了  伙计们  现在分开
All right, break it up, guys.
我们走
Let's go!
够了
That's enough.
你好
Hi, there.
对不起
Um, excuse me.
我想让你帮我个忙
I was wondering if you could help me.
我刚才在神奇小子上下了注
I placed a bet on SparkleKid for my boss.
-你知道发生什么了吗  -现在不行  美女
-Do you know what happened? -Not right now, sweetheart.
我老板让我
Okay. My boss had me
下的注比我一个星期挣得都多
put more money on him than I make in a week.
如果我告诉他发生了什么  他会疯的
Um, he's gonna flip out when I tell him about this.
和我谈没有用的
I'm really not the right person to ask.
但是  我在复仇虎鲸上压了500块钱
Okay, but, here, I put $500 here for Orca's Revenge.
-我可不可以  -你必须去和下注员谈
-Maybe I could...  -You're gonna have to talk to one of the window clerks.
我可不可以把刚才的钱都压在复仇虎鲸上
But maybe I could add it to that?
听着  我帮不了你
Look, I-I can't help you, all right?
美女 你最好现在就离开这里
Now, move it along, honey.
好吧
Okay, um, listen.
我只是想问你几个问题
I'm just trying to ask you a couple questions.
你问我太多问题了
Yeah, well, you asked one too many.
听听这个
How about this?
你能不能帮我
Why don't you help me find somebody
找个人解决我的问题 这样行了吧
who could help me sort all this out?How's that?
如果你不把手拿开
If you don't take your hands off me you're gonna
你会有比你老板更多的麻烦
have a lot more to worry about than an angry boss.
好吧 好吧
All right, well, um....
祝你有好的一天  长官
You take good care of yourself today, Officer.
对不起
Excuse me?
这里是禁止的区域  先生  你不能在这里
This is a restricted area, sir.You can't be back here.
我在找你们经理
Yeah, I'm looking for a manager
因为我要把我的钱要回来
because I'm getting the money back
那匹马的门竟然卡住了
that I bet on the horse that got stuck in the gate.
你刚才看见了
Did you see that one? Yeah.
我说了 你不能在这里  我需要支援
I said you can't be back here! I need back up.
你想干什么
What are you doing?
嘿
Hey!
-马宏在哪  -他在那儿
-Where's Mahone? -He's right there.
-这下糟了  设备在他身上  -我们搞砸了
-That's great.He's got the device. -We are screwed.
妈妈
Mommy?
宝贝 回你房间去 好吗
Go back to your room, okay, sweetheart.Okay.
天那  你怎么了
Oh, my God.What happened to you?
你好  妹妹
Hey, sis.
我们有问题了
We have an issue.
下午好  安迪
Good afternoon to you, too, Andy.
我刚才在查你
I've been reviewing your roster
东南区的销售单
from the Northeast division,
你的两个最大的买家的
and apparently two of your top buyers
社会保险号码是错的
don't have valid Social Security numbers.
能解释一下吗
Care to explain that?
我推销东西的时候
When I'm about to make a sale to a client,
我问我自己两个问题
I ask myself two questions:
这个对客户有用吗
"Is the client being helped?"
还有就是  我们能收到钱吗
and, "Are we gettin' paid?"
我当东北区最好的销售员
There's a reason
是有原因的
why I was the top seller in the Northeast.
我不拘小节
I don't get hung up on the details.
你的意思是
And what you're saying is...
在我的报表里有一两个错误是很正常的
There might be a typo or two in my reports,
但是我相信那些支票都兑现了
but I'm pretty sure those checks cleared.
嗯
Uh-huh.
好吧
Fair enough.
你早上一直很忙啊  弗兰克
You've had a busy morning, Frank.
非法进入  拘捕
Unlawful entry, resisting arrest.
还不到午餐时间
It's not even lunchtime.
你想吓唬我
You're trying to put the fear of God into me.
你做到了
Mission accomplished.
听着  警官
Listen, Sergeant,
我对司法系统有一定的了解
I know a decent amount about the justice system,
如果你愿意
enough to know that if you wanted to,
现在不起诉我
you could drop this whole thing and...
大家都会少很多的麻烦
it would save a lot of trouble for everybody, huh?
这是什么电话
What kind of phone is this?
是一个日本牌子  黑市买的
It's a, a Japanese brand. Off market.
那你脚腕上的监视器又是怎么回事
What about the ankle monitor you're wearing?
我跟你说的都是实话
I've been on the straight and narrow,
这个东西过几天就会摘下来
and it's due to come off in a couple of days.
按个手印
Press your fingers in the ink.
我刚才烟瘾犯了  我是个大烟枪
I had two grand go up in smoke because of a bum gate.
我的意思是  我刚才有一些紧张
I mean, I got a little upset for a second.
你知道我什么意思  谁都会这么做的
You know what I mean? Who wouldn't?
我们谈谈吧
Let's talk about this.
那我们就谈谈你打了一个警察一拳
Should we talk about how you punched an officer first?
而且你还想逃跑  你自己选一个吧
Or how you tried to flee the scene?Pick a felony.
带他去拘留所
Take him to the holding cell.
你说他被抓了
What do you mean he got arrested?
出什么事了
W-What happened?
说来话长
It's a long story,
但是我们需要你把他和仪器都带出来
but we need you to get Mahone and the device out.
你能做到吗
Can you do that?
你以为每次你们出事故
What do you think,that every time you guys screw up,
我就能帮你们全搞定
I can just magically make things disappear?
我们不管你什么借口
We ain't interested in your excuses.
你能不能做到
Can you do it or not?
林肯  我过一会再打给你
Lincoln, y-you know what? I'll call you back.
对不起  你是谁
Excuse me.Who are you?
-你在干什么  -我是布莱恩  IT组的
-What is this? -I'm Brian.I work in the IT department.
我们在服务器上发现
We were getting some registry inconsistencies
有些和登记不一样的地方
on the server, so...
我只是进行例行测试
I'm just running a few routine spot checks.
你不问问我就进来了
So you just barge in here without asking?
我有二级许可  看到没  这是我的工作
I have level two clearance. See?It's what I do.
我进大家的办公室  我修理电脑
I go into people's offices, I fix their computers.
我觉得你不在的时候把东西修好更好一点
I just figured it was better to do it when you weren't here.
告诉你  你现在就给我出去
Well, you know what? You got to go.
别再进来了
Don't come back in here.
没问题  我全搞定了
Sure thing.You're all set.
-怎么说  -赛尔夫正想办法
-So what's the word? -Self's on it.
意思是  他会把马宏弄出来
On it, as in he's getting Mahone out?
他说他来解决这个问题
He said he'd handle it.
有什么要解决的
What's there to handle?
我们这么大罪赛尔夫都能把我们弄出来
Self yanked us all out of prison for way bigger charges.
搞定马宏的事  不是更简单吗
Getting Mahone out should be easy, shouldn't it?
是啊
Yeah.
我们还是来找下一个持卡人吧
Let's concentrate on finding the next cardholder.
一旦我们拿回仪器  就继续复制
As soon as we get the device back, we'll move forward.
你能告诉我们  我们现在都知道什么吗
Would you please walk us through what we know so far?
好的
Sure.
霍华德·斯库得利经营的昂格里逊公司
Howard Scuderi runs AgriSow,
是世界上最大的农业集团
which is the world's largest agricultural conglomerate.
在老挝有大量的不动产
It actually has huge holdings in Laos,
而且现在还有通货膨胀
which, given the current inflation,
意味着他们赚钱易如反掌
means that they are making money hand over fist.
我的朋友在公园里玩
"My friends are playing at the park."
亲爱的  你先去房间里
Sweetheart, why don't you go play in your room
玩一会吧  好吗
for a little bit, okay?
-现在感觉如何  -好多了
-How are you feeling? -Better.
-我给你做了个三明治  -谢谢
-I, I made you a sandwich. -Thank you.
你不告诉我发生了什么吗
Um, you never explained what happened.
这样的
Well, um...
我的车在沙漠中坏了
my car broke down in the middle of the desert, and, uh...
而且附近都没有人  我的手机又没电了
there was no one around for miles,my cell phone was dead
所以我就走来了  你有没有留着我在德国
So I walked here. Hey, do you still have that owl
给你寄的那只猫头鹰
that I sent from Germany?
留着
Yeah.
-我想看看  -好的
-I need to see it.  -Okay.
谢谢
Thank you.
我的天啊  格雷琴
Oh, my God, Gretchen!
这个  这个是真的枪吗
Is that, is that, that a real gun?
是的
It is.
-你为美国国税局工作吗  -不是
-You don't work for the IRS? -I don't.
那你为谁工作
Who do you work for?
现在  我为自己
As of now? Myself.
他就读于长岛的杜鲁大学法学院
He attended Touro Law School in Long Island.
在02年进去国土安全局之前
He spent the next 18 years
他在内务部
bouncing around the D.O.J. and D.O.D. before being
和国防部呆了18年
dumped on the doorstep of Homeland in '02.
进来
Come in.
将军
General.
你发现什么了
What did you find out?
我尝试进去他的用户账户
I tried accessing Self's user account,
但他有一个非常复杂的防火墙系统
but he has a tricky firewall system in place.
不是很容易破解  除非
There's no easy way to get past it,not without...
我们花点精力
drawing attention.
所以我们仍然不知道他为什么对我感兴趣
So we still don't know why he's interested in me.
我需要更多的时间
Well, uh... maybe if you gave me more time.
让我来吧
I'll look into it.
听着  他对我很重要
Look, he's important to me.
他为我工作
Okay, he's doing a job for me.
你手下当着我的面  殴打我的人
Yeah, well, your CI punched one of my officers in the face.
我明白
I understand...
你要庆幸的是他不会受到很重的指控
You're lucky he's not being charged with worse.
我替他向你道歉  好吗
I apologize for him.Okay?
我想你帮我个忙
Look, I-I'm asking for a favor here,
好吗  看在我们是同行
okay, from one badge to another.
你最后一次审视你的徽章是什么时候
When was the last time you looked at your badge?
我很清楚自己的是由洛杉矶颁发
'Cause I'm pretty sure mine says issued by the
而不是由联邦政府颁发的
City of Los Angeles not the federal government,
-除非你有法院的命令  -嘿
So unless you get a court order that... -Hey, hey!
你要按照程序来吗  你要耍小聪明吗
You want to go that route? You want to get smart?
当你和你的情人见面返回后
Huh? Want to get detained at the Guadalajara airport
你想要在瓜达拉哈拉机场被拘留吗
when you're coming back from visiting your nana?
这听起来怎么样
How does that sound?
你有听过禁飞名单吗
Huh? You ever hear of a no-fly list?
这是我部门可以做到的事情  明白吧
That's what my badge could do.Okay?
还想知道其他我能做的吗
Want to see what else it could do?
我都有些担心了
I was starting to worry.
-签了这个  -好的
-Sign these. -Yeah.
-这个不是释放令  -我需要你签了它
-These aren't release papers. -Well, I need you to sign that
我才可以收集的你个人的
so I can collect your personal...
-他们要查我的指纹  -你刚打了一个警察
-They're gonna run my prints, and once they... -You punched a cop.
-是的  为了完成任务  -小声点  好吗
-Yeah, trying to save the mission. -Keep your voice down.Okay?
我已经尽力了
I did the best I could do.
你签了这个  我才可以拿到罗兰的设备
You need to sign those so I can collect Roland's device.
你是要我放弃
You... you want me to give up the one thing
我存在在这个组的意义
that makes me valuable to the team.
你加入的时候就应该知道了
Yeah, you knew the deal when you came on board.
为了这个我们都牺牲了很多
Okay, we all sacrificed a lot to get this far.
就因为你的行为
You want to flush it down the toilet
你想让这一切白费吗
because you made a bad move?
明白了
Got it.
赛尔夫拿到了设备  马宏还在监狱里
Self got the device.Mahone's still in jail.
可马宏是我们组的一员啊
But Mahone-- he-he's part of the team.
曾经是
Was.
对于他还有他的孩子  我和你们一样感到悲伤
Look, I feel just as bad about his kid as everyone else,
但我们不能为一个人而放弃任务
but we can't blow this mission on one person.
这样吗
Oh, yeah?
那么如果我明天被关了
So if I get popped tomorrow,
你们也这样放弃我
you guys are just going to forget about me?
是的
Yeah.
听着
Hey, listen.
有个杀手正在追杀我们
An assassin is trying to hunt us down, okay?
而通往城堡的钥匙以及
And that T-Bag character is out in the wind
蒂博格都还不知所踪
with the keys to the castle.
我们的问题已经够多了
We got enough problems
不要在想那个关押在监狱里的混蛋了
without having to worry about this guy's ass in jail.
你他妈给我闭嘴
You shut up.
好了
Okay.
阿历克斯用了假名  如果他们查他的指纹
Alex has an alias, but if they run his prints,
-他就知道他是  -不  如果
-they're gonna find out that he's... -Not if--
当他们查到他的指纹 他们就会查出他是谁
when they run his prints, they gonna figure out who he is
并且查明他应该呆在重刑监狱
and that he's not in a supermax like he's supposed to be,
他们不会意识到我们没
and then they're gonna realize  we're not...
迈克尔
Michael.
林肯说的对
Linc's right.
我们别无选择  我们按原计划行事
We don't have a choice.We move forward with the plan.
赛尔夫探员
Agent Self.
我是克兰兹将军的人
I'm an associate of General Krantz.
将军得到消息说
Word has gotten back to the General
你正在查他
that you've been pulling information on him.
赛尔夫先生  你为什么要如此
Why is that,Mr. Self?
我是国土安全局的
I'm Homeland Security.
我的工作就是保护像克兰兹这样
It's my job to protect people
是恐怖分子的首要攻击目标
who make attractive terrorist targets--
处于高度军事危险的人  免受伤害
people in upper ranks of military people like Krantz.
能告诉我具体是什么威胁吗?
Is there a particular threat I should know about?
或许你可以和我汇报下这个情况
Maybe you can debrief me on the situation.
你是哪个部门的
What's your division?
你能否出示下你的通行证等级
You want to give me your clearance level?
-我直接受雇于将军  -好吧
-I'm a... hired contractor.  -Right.
我通常不会把机密信息
Well,I usually don't make a habit of giving civilians who
透露给在地下停车场
corner me in underground parking structures
逼问我的平民  懂了吗?
classified information.Okay?
如果将军还有其他疑问  让他打电话给我
So if the General has a problem,he can call me.
你还有什么要对我说的吗?
Is there something else you want to say to me?
我想我们的首次交谈还算顺利
I think we got off on the wrong foot.
我只是来给你点友情建议
I'm just here to give you a little friendly advice.
什么建议?
What's that?
将军喜欢有自己的隐私
The General-- he likes his privacy.
仅此而已
That's all.
洛杉矶警局 停车场 11号
没错 他就是怀特
Yes, that was Wyatt.
我告诉你这个是因为
I gotta tell you,I'm not a big fan
我不想被人爆了头
of almost catching a bullet in my head.
现在你该知道这种感受了吧
Well,now you know what it's like.
你了解马宏多少
So,how well do you know Mahone?
我只知道他想搞垮"公司"就像我们那么强烈
I know he wants to take down the Company just as much as we do.
你还知道他是负有重大责任
You also realize he's a major liability.
我的意思是  如果怀特能找到我  他也能找到马宏
I mean,if Wyatt could find me,he could find Mahone.
并且...
And then people...
-那就把他弄出监狱  -我说了我做不到
-So get him out. -I told you I can't.
但是我能找到他  我是说我能联系上他
But I can get to him.I mean,he can be touched.
我也不知道 或许马宏是条汉子
I don't know,maybe Mahone is a stand-up guy.
或许他会供出我们来达到他的目的
Or maybe he likes to run his mouth to work an angle,
我不确定  但如果需要的话  我能除掉他
I'm not sure.But if need be,I can get rid of that angle.
-我能终结了这个威胁  -不予考虑
-I can eliminate that threat.-That's not an option.
不  考虑一下
Oh,yes it is.Okay,
因为如果要你选  是杀了他还是我们全玩儿完...
because if a choice has to be made between him or us...
弗兰克  给你带好消息来了
Hey,Frank.Got some good news.
是吗  什么好消息
Oh,yeah,what's that?
我能放了你
I can cut you a break.
就这么简单吗
As easy as that?
我和那个地铁站经理说过了
Spoke with the manager down at the racetrack.
他说一个比你小10岁左右的
Said you were spotted with another male Caucasian
白种人和你一起到过那
about ten years your junior.
说的没错吧
That sound about right?
警察来了
Here come the cops.
我不知道你在说什么
I have no idea what you're talking about.
到底怎么回事
What was it?
你们两个在那准备袭击押运车
The two of you were gonna go in there,rob the vault?
抢了现金就跑对吗
Grab as much cash and get out?
总得有个望风的
Someone has to be lookout.
我会看着的 快走!
I'll take care of it. Go!
瞧  或许你妻子正在家里等着你
Look.Maybe you got a wife to get home too.
你的整个家都在等你
Family.
如果你愿意供出你的同伙
If you're willing to give me the name of your accomplice
我想我们可以减轻对你的指控
I think we can change your charges.
我们是一伙的 你知道
I thought we worked together,you know.
-互相帮助  -你得靠你自己了
-Help each other out.-You're on your own.
如果你改变主意了就叫我
You holler if you change your mind.
现在我们谈谈这第五个持卡人
All right,let's talk about the fifth cardholder.
将军正要求
The General is requiring
所有持卡人必须把卡时刻带在自己身边
all the cardholders to have their cards on them at all times,
所以斯库得利也一定把卡带在身上
so Scuderi will have his card,too.
斯库得利的保安时刻巡视着他房子的四周
Now,Scuderi has major security around his house.
大围墙围着他的房子  还有一群狗看着
Big fence,lots of guard dogs.
文件在哪
Where are the documents?
这些是从县督察员办公室拿来的
These are from the county surveyor's office.
这是他房子的布局图
It shows the layout of his property,
以及他接近街道处的所有建筑
and its proximity to every other house on his street.
他有着绝对顶级的
He has-- surprise,surprise--
电子警报系统
a top of the line electronic alarm system
一旦有人入侵  警报就会启动
that will alert him if there's a breach in the structure.
如果我切断电源  警报就会消除
If we cut the power-- the alarm goes off.
如果我们用突增的瞬间电压  增加电力供应
if we double the power with a voltage spike
这个警报系统会为了保护自身装置
the alarm system,in order to protect itself
免受超载 它会自动关闭
against an overload, will shut itself down.
我们就那么进去
And that's how we're getting in.
然后呢
Then what?
我知道该怎么做  每人搞定自己那部分
Look, I know what the score is.It's every man for himself.
你慢了就完蛋  真他妈难搞
You get left behind you get locked up.Tough titties.
现在我跟其他人一样都签了字
Now, I signed on the dotted line
我想清楚的知道
like everyone else and I want to know exactly
我该做什么
what I'm doing on this job.
我和贝里克一起
I'm with Bellick on this one.
我觉得在警察来之前
You know, maybe
我们得有个计划
we should have a plan for when the cops get here
因为如果马宏告密的话他们很快就会回来
'cause if Mahone squeals they're gonna come real quick.
他是联邦政府官员  你觉得他一生中
He's a Fed-- how many deals
作过多少交易
do you think this guy's made in his life?
你觉得他会夹起尾巴
You think he's just gonna tuck tail between his...
闭嘴
Shut up.
我们大可以在这坐着讨论一天
Look, we can sit here and debate
看马宏会做或不会做什么
what Mahone is or is not gonna do for the rest of the day,
但问题是
but it comes down to this:
我们不能把他从警局给弄出来
we cannot break him out of a police station.
一  二
One... two...
三  四  五  六
three, four, five, six--
不  太大了
No. Too big.
八乘以十
Eight by ten.
这是我能弄到的最低限度
This is the lowest gauge I could get.
好极了
It's perfect.
我觉得  我觉得我们只能让他呆监狱里了
I guess, uh...I guess we're gonna leave him in jail.
你是在陈述还是在问
Is that a statement or a question?
如果阿历克斯有什么事的话
It's just if something happens to Alex--
如果公司找到他
if, uh, if the Company finds him...
如果角色互换  换做是你被抓
If the roles were reversed and you were the one locked up,
你觉得阿历克斯会冒险来救你吗
you really think Alex would risk it all to get you out?
我不知道
I mean, I don't know.
但是  他是联邦探员
But...he was a federal agent.
我觉得他会有始有终
I think he'd finish what he started.
我相信他会设法搞垮公司
I think he'd bring the Company down.
有什么能帮您吗
Can I help you with something?
我是来找弗兰克·斯万的
Yes, I-I'm here to see Frank Zwan.
我是他们家世交
I'm a family friend.
恐怕你现在不能见他
I'm afraid you can't see him right now.
他正要接受传讯
He's about to be transferred for his arraignment.
我是想来提供精神支持的
Actually, I'd like to be there for moral support.
能告诉我法庭在哪吗
Could you tell me where's the court house?
喂
Hello?
迈克尔
Michael.
阿历克斯  很抱歉
Alex, look, I'm sorry.
他发现我了
He found me.
怀特  他出现在警局
Wyatt-- He showed up at the station house
他们抓住了我  我不知道他怎么找到我的
where they're holding me. I don't know how he did it.
不知道他怎么查出来了
I don't know how he figured it out.
我打电话给赛尔夫
Let me call Agent Self.
不  迈克尔  听着
No, Michael, listen...
不  可能他们会转移你
No, maybe he can get you moved.
我完了  全完了
It's-it's over for me. It's done.
我什么都不会说的
It's-- and I'm not gonna say anything about anything.
但你得答应我件事  可以吗
But you need to promise me something, okay?
-好的  是什么  -答应我
-Okay, what? -Promise me...
你去找怀特  杀了那狗娘养的
that you will get to Wyatt and you'll kill the son of a bitch.
然后打电话给帕姆
And then you'll call Pam
告诉她我死了
and you'll tell her that he's gone.
好的
All right.
我答应你
I promise.
好  再见
Ok. Bye.
准备好了吗  迈克尔
You ready to go?Michael?
我是他老婆
I'm his wife.
抱歉  我还是没很震惊
I'm sorry, I'm-I'm still in shock.
我下午过来
I'll be down this afternoon.
谢谢
Thank you.
你到底在干嘛
Who are you?
我有事要处理
I just have some things I need to take care of.
你不用担心
You don't need to worry.
你总是把人拒之于外
You have this...switch inside you.
我不知道你是怎么会
I don't know how you could just...
自我封闭起来的
shut yourself off.
妈妈死的时候你这样  对艾米丽也是这样
You did it when Mom died.Did it with Emily.
这么对我
Did it with me.
我这么做是因为  我就是这样的
I do it because it's...it's just who I am.
不  不是的  以前你
No, it's not.You used to be...
我得走了  但谢谢你  为了这一切
I have to go.But thank you... for everything.
你不是来带她走的
So, you're not here to take her?
如果我能个好母亲
If I was capable of being her mother,
我就不会把监护权给你了
I wouldn't have given you custody.
你会听话的  是不是
You be a good girl, okay?
-艾米丽  再见  -婶婶再见
-Bye, Emily. -Bye, Auntie.
我爱你
I love you.
-我们还能再见面吗  -我不知道
-Will we see you again? -I don't know.
要是去南边就给我电话
Call me if it goes south.
亲爱的  是我  我在杂货店
Hey,honey.it's me.I'm at the grocery store.
我打算做烤猪排
I was planning to make those grilled pork chops,
除非你不想吃
unless you're not in the mood for them.
希望你今天愉快
I hope you're having a great day.
你们在干什么
Hey, what are you guys doing?
我们完成了再给你电话
We'll call you when we're done.
等等
Wait.
你们在哪
Where are you guys?
马上好了
Almost ready.
你有麻烦了
You have a problem.
怎么了
What's that?
有什么能效劳的
What can I do you for?
我刚刚发现了更多不一致的地方
I just-- I've found some more inconsistencies
你的销售报告里  实际上  非常多
in your sales reports.Actually, many more.
事实上  有点像是欺诈
In fact...kind of looks like fraud, actually.
我从一开始就知道你很垃圾
I knew you were rotten from the beginning.
我要你5分钟内到我办公室
I want you in my office in five minutes
给我解释清楚
to walk me through this,
你要是做不到
and if you can't,
我就打电话给当局
well, I'm gonna call the authorities.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
很高兴认识你  甜心
Nice knowing you, sugar.
科尔  等等
Cole, wait.
他去世时我在国外
I was traveling abroad when he passed away.
同样  我很抱歉
Again, I'm very sorry.
这是你丈夫吗
Is this your husband?
是的
Yes.
我要看到证明
I need to see some identification
我才能签字移交他的私人物品给你
so I can sign over his personal belongings to you.
你跟你爱人的姓氏不同
So... you and your spouse had different last names?
没错
That's correct.
我知道这很麻烦
I realize this is an inconvenience,
但我得看到其他能证明
but I need to see other documentation
你们已婚的文件
proving you were married.
你知道我经历过什么事吗
Do you have any idea what I've been through?
抱歉  女士  规定就是规定
I'm sorry, ma'am.Rules are rules.
你好  普发先生  我是英斯多霍姆公司的克丽丝朵
WO Hey, Mr. Pfeiffer, this is Crystal from Instahomes
给你回电话  只想通知你
getting back to you.Just wanted to let you know
你的押金已经到账
that your security deposit check cleared
卧房也准备好了  谢谢
and your one bedroom is ready. Thank you.
我是弗兰克·斯万的代表
Hi, I'm, uh, representing Frank Zwan.
我要他的资料
I'm going to need his jacket from you.
他们通知我  说他没钱请律师
I've been informed he's going indigent.
以前是
Uh, he was.
她妈妈在圣巴巴拉市  可有的是钱
His mother in Santa Barbara, however, is not,
她今天早上雇了我
and she retained me this morning.
请便
Be my guest.
非常感激
Much obliged.
Five.
Four.
Three.
先生
Sir.
Two.
请坐下
Please take a seat.
One.
好了  我们走
All right,Let's get out of here.
我不知道你们...
I don't know if, uh, you guys...
这么做是为了队伍还是为了我  而且...
did this for the team or if you did it for me, and...
我不在乎
I don't care.
我只是...
I just...
谢谢你们
Thank you.
喂
Yes.
我收到你的信息了
I got your message.
我还在想你什么时候会回电话
I was wondering when you were going to call.
你跟我妻子说你要我自投罗网
You told my wife you wanted me to turn myself in.
那你为何不告诉我去哪能和你见面
So, uh, why don't you tell me where to go and I'll meet you?
我们做个了断
Let's get this over with.
这件事可没那么快了结  阿历克斯
This thing is far from over,Alex.
首先  我在这找到莎拉·唐克雷蒂
First I find Sara Tancredi here,
然后是你
then you.
看来我们要谈的事还相当多
Seems like there's a great deal of things for us to talk about.
不
Oh, no.
No.
我和你之间只有一件事可谈
There's only one thing for you and I to discuss.
你曾为公司卖过命  阿历克斯
You worked for the Company once, Alex.
你应该知道不能太感情用事
You should know better than to take things so personally.
我会把这个收拾掉
I'm gonna wrap this up,
以防你会跟踪这个电话
just in case you decided to trace this call,
我向你保证
but I promise you...
我们会再见  到那时
We will meet again, and when we do,
我会让你知道这有多感情用事
I'm going to show you just how personal things can get.
没错
Oh, yeah.
科尔·普发
Cole Pfeiffer.
现在要怎么办
What you gonna do now?
你究竟是谁
Who the hell are you?